date.com 2004-04-02

# Date.com - Join Now for Free!

This statement discloses the information gathering process and the privacy and dissemination practices for the Date.com Web site. Date.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protect your personal privacy. 

Date.com is an internet singles portal designed to provide an easy way to meet other singles on the internet. Members create a profile and are then paired with a number of other members based on their pre-selected dating criteria. None of the information requested can be used by the public to identify a specific individual. This includes visitors, other members, anyone not employed by Date.com, its corporate affiliates, or the financial institutions we use to process membership fees. 

Date.com is a membership-based service that collects credit card numbers, addresses, and bank information only from those who choose to sign up as paid members. Any visitors to Date.com may choose to browse the site, search the profiles and/or view any articles by signing up for a free trial membership. 

Date.com's registration form requires users to provide contact information such as an email address and demographic information (such as zip code, age, or income level). Date.com also occasionally runs contests and conducts online surveys that ask visitors for contact information such as name and email address and demographic information such as zip code, age, or income level. 

Date.com contains links to other web sites and Date.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

**Private, Public and Aggregate Information obtained by Date.com**

PRIVATE INFORMATION is any information that allows others to contact a user other than through Date.com or allows the collection of information about the user other than what is displayed on the site. Private information is gathered from free trial members and regular members. This information includes, but is not limited to: email address, IP address, first name, last name, credit card number, and address. 

PUBLIC INFORMATION is personal information that may be displayed on the site, such as gender, age and height, but cannot be linked to a particular user. Public information is personal information such as gender, age, ethnic background, appearance, and more. This information is meant to be seen by members and visitors to the site but cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, or other profile information. Members can post images of themselves but no identifying information is allowed to be posted with that image. 

AGGREGATE: This is information we collect that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered from all visitors to the site. 

**Use of Information Obtained by Date.com**

PRIVATE INFORMATION: We use email addresses submitted by members when forwarding anonymous emails. Respondees' email addresses are not disclosed to the responder nor is any other personally identifiable information. We may use a user's email address to send news regarding our site or offers we feel appropriate to our members but with the exception of specific direct marketing emails following the free trial period, the user may choose not to receive email of this type by indicating upon joining up to not receive such mail or later at any time through our unsubscribe methods or by modifying their account information. 

Email addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for services. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law or to protect members of Date.com. All private information can be updated or deleted by the user at any time. 

PUBLIC INFORMATION: Public information supplied by the user is intended to be viewed by registrants and subscribers to the site. This information is used by registrants and subscribers for searching and matching purposes.   
AGGREGATE: We use your server, IP address, and browser-type related information in the general administration of our website. It is not personally identifiable information and is not released to third parties. 

**Chat Rooms, Bulletin Boards, and Forums**

Date.com makes chat rooms available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information online. 

**Use of Cookies**

We currently use cookies in our Chat areas and for our own advertising purposes. Please note that advertisers on the Date.com site may send cookies to users of the site and Date.com does not control or have access to this information. 

**Change/Delete**

Date.com gives trial members and paid members an option for modifying or removing their information from our database. Your privacy is one of our highest priorities. 

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy of Date.com, please email them to abuse@date.com.
